UX/UI designer

Summary:

UX/UI Designer striving to create meaningful, engaging, accessible and pleasant experiences. I am solution oriented and collaborative and try to combine usability, creativity and fun. Primarily skilled in UX and UI Design, but also in illustration and photography.

Skills: Prototyping & Wireframing | Usability Testing | UI Design | UX Research | HTML5 & CSS

Tools: Figma | Sketch | InVision | Principle | Zeplin | Adobe Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, XD) | VS Code | GitHub

Projects:

Wine Access design (<u>link to the project</u>), Wine Access, San Francisco, CA March 2019 - Present Full website design, from conceptualization and user research, to design execution and production, including developing wireframes, userflow diagrams, all visual elements, layouts and photographs.

Bootcamp spot redesign (<u>link to the project</u>), *Trilogy Education***, San Francisco, CA April 2020 - May 2020 Redesign of BCS website to optimize it for users' needs and maximize students' return of investment.**

Healthier Kids Foundation redesign (link to the project), San Jose, CA February 2020 - March 2020 Website redesign of a non-profit organization that gives children the education and medical care.

Experience

UX/UI Designer, AI Fund, Palo Alto, CA

2020 - Present

Research, conceptualization of UX flows and design of visual components for various AI Fund projects.

Senior UX/UI and Visual Designer, Wine Access, San Francisco, CA

2019 - Present

Responsible for all aspects of design, from conceptualization, to design execution and production, including web redesign, developing concepts, graphics, photographs and layouts for marketing materials, social media visuals, emails, web pages, wine labels and other media.

- Fully redesigned website to make it responsive, increase accessibility, improve overall user experience and gain business goals
- Built company's design system that is being used throughout departments
- Redesigned email template which increased click through rate by 52%

UX/UI Designer, Women in Tech Oslo, Oslo, Norway

2018 - 2019

- Created logo and defined visual identity
- Designed responsive website

UX/UI Designer, *Weekndr*, Oslo, Norway

2017 - 2018

- Designed (UX/UI) Weekndr Facebook chatbot as well as website and mobile app concepts
- · Created visual identity and UI elements

Education:

UX/UI design bootcamp certificate, UC Berkeley, San Francisco

2019 - 2020

An intensive 24-week long bootcamp dedicated to UX/UI design with focus on research and front-end development. Skills learned consist of User research, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, jQuery, User-Centric Design Research, Visual Prototyping & Wireframing, User Interface Development.